OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/020
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Private agreements: Code nos.2973-3674 (Box 28)
  - 2980, 1989-1998 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    5/1989 - 5/1998; contains agreement booklets
  - 3222, 1986-1994 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    5/1986 - 10/1994; contains agreement booklets
  - 3255, 1980-1998 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    5/1980 - 5/1998; contains agreement booklets
  - 3225, 1979-1990 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    9/1979 - 9/1990; contains agreement booklets
  - 3399, 1989-2001 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    10/1/1989 - 10/1/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 3398, 1992-2001 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    10/6/1992 - 10/5/2001
  - 3397, 1976-1995 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    11/1976 - 2/1995; contains agreement booklets
  - 3293, 1982-1993 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    10/1982 - 6/1993; contains agreement booklets
  - 3287, 1987-1996 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    6/1987 - 6/1996; contains agreement booklets
  - 3674, 1990-1993 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    1/1990 - 2/1993; contains agreement booklet
  - 3661, 2001-2004 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    4/2001 - 4/2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 3629, 1988-2002 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    8/1988 - 8/2002; contains agreement booklets
  - Folder List Index Box # 28 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Public agreements: Code nos.830298-830646 (Box 29)
  - 830278, 1998-2002 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    School District # 1 Multnomah County
  - 830281, 2004-2006 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Douglas County School District 0001
  - 830299, 2001-2003 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - 830301, 2003-2006 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Lansing School District Board of Education
  - 830311, 2002-2005 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    School District #1 City and County of Denver
  - 830312, 2003-2006 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Regional Transportation District
  - 830324, 2000-2004 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Cleveland Board of Education
  - 830331, 2003-2006 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Spokane School District 81
  - 830348, 1991-1994 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Dearborn Board of Education
  - 830353, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    Board of Education Madison Metro School District
  - 830408, 2004-2006 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    Toledo Board of Education and Employment
  - 830412, 2000-2003 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    Manchester NH Board of School Committee
  - 830420, 2004-2006 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    Special School District #1
  - 830421, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    830422 Public Schools
  - 830422, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    Board of Education Unified School District 259
  - 830424, 2003-2006 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    Rhode Island Hospital
  - 830425, 2001-2004 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    County of Union
  - 830442, 2004-2006 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - 830443, 2004-2006 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - 830454, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - 830457, 2000-2005 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    Board of Trustees University of Illinois
  - 830458, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    State of Maryland
  - 830459, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - 830460, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - 830461, 2000-2003 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - 830470, 2002-2005 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    Wayne State University
  - 830474, 2000-2003 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    Lodi Unified School District
  - 830475, 2001-2004 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    Broward Sheriffs Office
  - 830483, 2003-2006 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    Board of Education Youngstown City School District
  - 830505, 2002-2004 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    Board of Education of Anne Arundel County
  - 830522, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    Anoka-Hennepin Independent School District
  - 830532, 2001-2003 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    Hawaii State University
  - 830533, 1997-1999 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    State of Hawaii Board of Regents
  - 830534, 2004-2006 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    City of Memphis, Tennessee
  - 830535, 2004-2006 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    City of Memphis, Tennessee Firefighters
  - 830536, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    School Board of Independence
  - 830541, 2003-2006 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    Des Moines Independent Community School District
  - 830554, 2002-2005 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    Board of Education of Howard County
  - 830555, 2002-2005 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - 830579, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 40)
    Board of Education Decatur Public School District #61
  - 830587, 2003-2006 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - 830588, 1987-1990 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - 830598, 2001-2004 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    Mt. Diablo School District
  - 830629, 2003-2006 (Box 29, Folder 44)
    Bakersfield City School District
  - 830630, 2002-2005 (Box 29, Folder 45)
    Duval County School Board
  - 830645, 2004-2005 (Box 29, Folder 46)
    Phoenix Union High School District
  - 830646, 2001-2006 (Box 29, Folder 47)
    School Board Broward County
  - Folder List Index Box # 29 (Box 29, Folder 48)
- Private agreements: Code nos.3737-4028 (Box 30)
  - 3737, 1989-1998 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    12/1989 - 12/1998; contains agreement booklets
  - 3745, 1994-1998 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    9/1994 - 11/1998; contains agreement booklets
  - 3747, 1988-2003 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    9/1988 - 9/2003; contains agreement booklets
  - 3748, 1988-1994 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    1/1988 - 1/1994; contains agreement booklets
  - 3749, 1988-1992 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    3/1988 - 3/1992
  - 3780, 1985-2003 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    8/1985 - 8/2003; contains agreement booklets
  - 3787, 1989-1998 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - 3806, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    10/1994; contains agreement booklet
  - 3807, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    6/12/1996
  - 4019, 1993-1999 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    10/4/1993 - 9/14/1999; contains agreement booklets
  - 4028, 1980-1993 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    10/1980 - 5/1993; contains agreement booklets
  - Folder List Index Box # 30 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Private agreements: Code nos.8413-9021 (Box 31)
  - 8413, 1988-1998 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    7/1988 - 6/1998; contains agreement booklet
  - 8426, 1997-2001 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    3/1997 - 3/2001; contains agreement booklet
  - 8440, 1989-2006 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    5/1989 - 4/2006; contains agreement booklets
  - 8459, 1990-1993 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    3/1990 - 3/1993
  - 8328, 1995-2003 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    6/1995 - 5/2003; contains agreement booklet
  - 8504, 1988-2003 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    11/1988 - 6/2003
  - 8584, 1987-1997 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    7/1987 - 7/1997; contains agreement booklet
  - 8606, 1989-2002 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    6/1989 - 5/2002; contains agreement booklets
  - 8607, 1992-2002 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    6/1992 - 5/2002; contains agreement booklets
  - 8629, 1997-2000 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    8/1997 - 5/2000
  - 8630, 1975-1989 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    4/1975 - 4/1989; contains agreement booklet
  - 8642, 1998-2004 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    6/1998 - 2/2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 8643, 1998-2004 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - 8644, 1998-2004 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    5/1998 - 5/2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 8644, 1989-1992 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    5/1989 - 4/1992
  - 8706, 1986-2003 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    7/1986 - 6/2003; contains agreement booklet
  - 8726, 1980-2006 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    12/1980 - 12/2006; contains agreement booklets
  - 8733, 1988-1992 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    4/1988 - 3/1992; contains agreement booklet
  - 8894, 1979-1990 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    8/1979 - 5/1990; contains agreement booklet
  - 8919, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    3/1996
  - 8924, 1986-1994 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    2/1986 - 6/1994; contains agreement booklets
  - 8939, 1976-1992 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    6/1976 - 6/1992
  - 8949, 1985-1994 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    4/1985 - 4/1994; contains agreement booklets
  - 8950, 1982-1994 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    7/1982 - 5/1994; contains agreement booklets
  - 8665, 1989-1995 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    5/1989 - 4/1995
  - 8669, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    4/1987 - 5/1988; contains agreement booklet
  - 8954, 1984-1986 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - 9002, 1981-1992 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    5/1981 - 6/1992; contains agreement booklets
  - 9003, 1968-1989 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    11/1968 - 11/1989; contains agreement booklets
  - 9014, 1994-1997 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    5/1994 - 5/1997
  - 9017, 1973-1988 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    4/1973 - 12/1988
  - 9018, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    6/1998; contains agreement booklet
  - 9020, 1990-1997 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    1/1990 - 1/1997
  - 9021, 1994-1997 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    4/1994 - 4/1997
  - Folder List Box # 31 (Box 31, Folder 35)
- Private agreements: Code nos.1628-1681 (Box 32)
  - 1628, 1992-2003 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    6/1992 - 10/2003; contains agreement booklets
  - 1630, 1995-2004 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    2/1995 - 2/2004; contains agreement booklets
  - 1642, 1991-1994 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    4/1991 - 4/1994; contains agreement booklets
  - 1649, 1984-1993 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    3/1984 - 3/1993; contains agreement booklets
  - 1657, 1974-1993 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    5/1974 - 10/1993; contains agreement booklets
  - 1667, 1983-1992 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    3/1983 - 3/1992; contains agreement booklets
  - 1675, 1968-1993 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    4/1968 - 6/1993; contains agreement booklets
  - 1681, 1976-1994 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    2/1976 - 2/1994; contains agreement booklets
  - Folder List Index Box # 32 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Private agreements: Code nos.7969-8001 (Box 33)
  - 7969, 1990-2002 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    7/1990 - 6/2002; contains agreement booklets
  - 7981, 1973-1996 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    3/1973 - 2/1996; contains agreement booklets
  - 7985, 1968-2004 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    1/1968 - 12/2004; contains agreement booklets
  - 7986, 1967-2003 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    1/1967 - 12/2003; contains agreement booklets
  - 7987, 1972-1984 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    3/1972 - 6/1984; contains agreement booklet
  - 7990, 1994-2000 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    November 1 1994 - October 31 2000
  - 7996, 1982-2001 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    3/1982 - 10/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 7999, 1980-1988 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    10/1980 - 9/1988; contains agreement booklets
  - 8000, 1990-1993 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    10/1990-10/1993
  - 8001, 1987-2001 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    7/1987 - 7/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - Folder List Index Box # 33 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Private agreements: Code nos.4128-4428 (Box 34)
  - 4128, 1970-1991 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    2/1970 - 7/1991; contains agreement booklets
  - 4129, 1972-1987 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    6/1972 - 9/1987; contains agreement booklets
  - 4132, 1972-1992 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    3/1972 - 6/1992; contains agreement booklets
  - 4137, 1971-1991 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    12/1971 - 12/1991; contains agreement booklets
  - 4147, 1972-1993 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    6/1972 - 6/1993; contains agreement booklets
  - 4151, 1973-1990 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    1/1973 - 5/1990; contains agreement booklets
  - 4169, 1970-1993 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    10/1970 - 10/1993; contains agreement booklets
  - 4184, 1971-1989 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    8/1971 - 4/1989; contains agreement booklets
  - 4193, 1978-1990 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    7/1978 - 7/1990
  - 4202, 1991-1997 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    3/1991 - 3/1997; contains agreement booklets
  - 4204, 1989-1992 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    12/1989 - 12/1992; contains agreement booklets
  - 4428, 1974-1989 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    1/1974 - 1/1989
  - Folder List Index Box # 34 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Public agreements: Code nos.810443-810749 (Box 35)
  - 810443, 2000-2003 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - 810444, 2002-2005 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - 810445, 2002-2005 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - 810446, 2000-2002 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - 810447, 2002-2004 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    Ohio Turnpike Company
  - 810454, 1996-1997 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    City of Anaheim
  - 810456, 2000-2002 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - 810460, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - 810482, 2004-2005 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    Mayor and City Council of Baltimore
  - 810492, 1996-1999 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    City of Boston
  - 810505, 2001-2004 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    City of Cincinnati
  - 810507, 2002-2004 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - 810508, 2002-2005 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    University of Cincinnati
  - 810567, 1978-1988 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    City of Buffalo
  - 810570, 2002-2005 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    City and AFSCME Local
  - 810591, 2000-2002 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - 810598, 2002-2005 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    City of Rochester, NY
  - 810599, 2001-2003 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    DC, Government and Compensation Union 1 and 2
  - 810612, 2001-2003 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    City of Milwaukee
  - 810613, 2001-2005 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    City of Pittsburgh
  - 810614, 2001-2004 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    Nashville Firefighters
  - 810619, 2001-2003 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - 810621, 2002-2005 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    City of Philadelphia
  - 810632, 1998-2001 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    City of Detroit
  - 810635, 2003-2006 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    City of Seattle
  - 810636, 2003-2005 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    City of Jacksonville
  - 810637, 1999-2001 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - 810643, 2004-2006 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    City of Portland, Oregon
  - 810647, 2004-2005 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - 810649, 2003-2006 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    School Board of Osceola County, Florida
  - 810656, 2002-2005 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    Miami-Dade County, Florida
  - 810657, 2002-2005 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    Miami-Dade County, Florida Public Health Trust
  - 810658, 2003-2005 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - 810661, 2001-2004 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    Fraternal Order of Police, Andrew Jackson #5
  - 810662, 2000-2003 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - 810663, 2000-2003 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - 810664, 2000-2003 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - 810665, 1999-2000 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    The School Board of Osceola County, Florida
  - 810699, 2003-2004 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    Elgin Teacher Association
  - 810743, 1988-1990 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - 810748, 1998-2001 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - 810749, 2004-2005 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Folder List Index Box # 35 (Box 35, Folder 43)
- Private agreements: Code nos.K4083-K5226 (Box 36)
  - 4079, 2000-2003 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    BIW
  - 4083, 2001-2004 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    Boeing
  - 4084, 1999-2003 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - 4085, 2001-2006 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    GKN Aerospace
  - 4088, 2003-2006 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    Goodrich Aerostructures
  - 4091, 2000-2005 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    Solar Turbines
  - 4093, 2002-2006 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    Sikorsky
  - 4096, 2001-2004 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    Pratt and Whitney
  - 4104, 2001-2006 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    General Dynamics
  - 4108, 1999-2004 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    Northrup Grumman Newport News
  - 4116, 2000-2005 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    Rolls Royce
  - 4129, 1988-1992 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    National Steel and Ship Building
  - 4133, 2001-2004 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    Mack Trucks
  - 4154, 1996-2005 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    AM General
  - 4164, 2001-2005 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    Mitsubishi
  - 4177, 2002-2005 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - 4183, 1997-2002 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    Howmet
  - 4193, 2001-2004 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    Aerospace Corp
  - 4194, 2001-2006 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    Honeywell
  - 4197, 2001-2005 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    New United Motor Manufacturing
  - 4201, 2002-2005 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    Todd Pacific Shipyards
  - 4205, 2003-2006 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    Freightliner
  - 4208, 2001-2005 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - 4412, 2002-2006 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    Lockheed Martin
  - 4427, 2002-2005 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    Xerox
  - 4607, 1973-2000 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    Metro Association of Doll, Stuffed Toy and Plastics Manufacturers
  - 5217, 2002-2005 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    New York Movers and Warehousemen
  - 5226, 1976-1998 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    National Master Freight
  - Folder List Index Box # 36 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Private agreements: Code nos.1809-1915 (Box 37)
  - 1915, 1997-2003 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    11/1997 - 4/2003; contains agreement booklets
  - 1908, 1991-2003 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    9/1991 - 4/2003; contains agreement booklets
  - 1829, 1973-1988 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    2/1973 - 3/1988; contains agreement booklets
  - 1825, 1979-1990 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    3/1979 - 3/1990; contains agreement booklets
  - 1818, 1971-1993 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    1/1971 - 2/1993; contains agreement booklets
  - 1815, 1973-1993 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    4/1973 - 6/1993; contains agreement booklets
  - 1812, 1979-1993 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    1/1979 - 1/1993; contains agreement booklets
  - 1813, 1971-1990 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    1/1971 - 1/1990; contains agreement booklets
  - 1809, 1979-1993 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Public agreements: Code nos.830755-830814 (Box 38)
  - 830755, 1999-2002 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    Board of Education San Diego Unified School District
  - 830756, 2001-2004 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    San Diego Unified School District
  - 830757, 2003-2006 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    School Board of Miami-Dade County
  - 830758, 2003-2006 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    California State University
  - 830760, 2003-2005 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    Kenosha Unified School District 1
  - 830762, 2002-2005 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    State Board of Trustees Hartford Public Schools
  - 830763, 1997-2005 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    School Board of Seminole County
  - 830764, 2002-2005 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Sacramento City Unified School District
  - 830765, 2003-2006 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    School Board of Lee County
  - 830766, 2005-2006 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - 830767, 1992-1993 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - 830769, 2005-2006 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    School Board of Orange County, Florida
  - 830770, 1999-2002 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Board of Education Syracuse City School District
  - 830771, 2000-2002 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    Springfield School Committee
  - 830772, 2001-2003 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    Board of Education City of Yonkers
  - 830773, 2003-2004 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    Bridgeport Board of Education
  - 830774, 2001-2004 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    Manatee County School Board
  - 830775, 2002-2005 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    Los Angeles Unified School District
  - 830776, 2004-2006 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    School Board of Pinellas County
  - 830778, 1991-1993 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    Independent School District 196
  - 830779, 2002-2005 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    School Board of Bay County, Florida
  - 830780, 2003-2006 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    Bay District School Board
  - 830781, 2003-2006 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    Independent School District 709
  - 830782, 2002-2004 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    Stamford Board of Education
  - 830783, 2000-2003 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    Garden Grove Unified School District
  - 830784, 1990-1992 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - 830787, 1999-2002 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    Fort Wayne Community School
  - 830788, 2002-2006 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    Board of Trustees of University of Illinois
  - 830790, 2002-2005 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    San Diego Community College
  - 830792, 2003-2004 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    Jordan School District
  - 830793, 1999-2003 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    Livonia Public Schools
  - 830795, 1995-1997 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - 830796, 2003-2006 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - 830797, 2001-2004 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    San Juan Unified School District
  - 830798, 2003-2006 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - 830799, 1993-1995 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - 830800, 2002-2004 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    Board of Education Albuquerque School District
  - 830804, 2001-2004 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - 830805, 2001-2003 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    Jefferson Parish LA School Board
  - 830806, 1999-2002 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    Miami-Dade County Public School
  - 830807, 2003-2006 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - 830810, 2003-2004 (Box 38, Folder 42)
    Oakland Unified School District
  - 830813, 2003-2004 (Box 38, Folder 43)
    Davenport Community School District
  - 830814, 2001-2005 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Folder List Index Box # 38 (Box 38, Folder 45)
- Private agreements: Code nos.6034-6375 (Box 39)
  - 6034, 1990-2003 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    7/1/1990 - 7/1/2003; contains agreement booklets
  - 6035, 1990-2003 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    7/1/1990 - 6/30/2003; contains agreement booklets
  - 6038, 1992-2001 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    1/26/1992 - 1/26/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 6040, 1995-2001 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    8/1995 - 8/15/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 6045, 1988-2002 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    10/1/1988 - 4/1/2002; contains agreement booklets
  - 6067, 1992-2001 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    11/11/1992 - 11/10/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 6069, 1974-1990 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    8/1974 - 5/1990; contains agreement booklets
  - 6076, 1984-1989 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    4/1984 - 4/1989
  - 6078, 1974-1990 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    1/1974 - 9/1990; contains agreement booklets
  - 6089, 1989-1998 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    7/1/1989 - 6/30/1998; contains agreement booklets
  - 6096, 1987-2001 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    10/1/1987 - 10/1/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 6103, 1995-2003 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    5/12/1995 - 5/11/2003; contains agreement booklets
  - 6302, 1998-2002 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    9/14/1998 - 9/15/2002
  - 6348, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    7/2001; contains agreement booklet
  - 6351, 1997-2000 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    10/1997 - 10/8/2000; contains agreement booklets
  - 6363, 1996-2003 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    6/30/1996 - 4/1/2003
  - 6368, 1998-2002 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    10/11/1998 - 7/6/2002
  - 6369, 1998-2002 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - 6373, 1999-2004 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    1/31/1999 - 1/31/2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 6375, 1999-2003 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    5/1/1999 - 4/30/2003
  - Folder List Index Box # 39 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Public agreements: Code nos.820346-820794 (Box 40)
  - 820346, 1992-1994 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    Westchester County
  - 820348, 2000-2003 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    County of Erie
  - 820349, 2000-2003 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - 820350, 2001-2003 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    County of Chautauqua
  - 820351, 2000-2004 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    County of Saratoga
  - 820356, 1992-1995 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    Suffolk County
  - 820359, 2000-2004 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    County of Wayne
  - 820365, 2001-2004 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    Dutchess County
  - 820368, 1978-1980 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    County of Chemung
  - 820375, 1986-1988 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    County of Livingston
  - 820377, 2000-2003 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    Monroe County
  - 820383, 2002-2005 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    County of Ulster
  - 820384, 2000-2002 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    County of Orange
  - 820389, 2003-2005 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    County of Broome
  - 820419, 2003-2006 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    Palm Beach County Board
  - 820420, 2002-2005 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    School Board of Lake County
  - 820421, 2003-2006 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    District School Board of Collier County
  - 820436, 2003-2006 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    County of Los Angeles
  - 820456, 2004-2005 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    Hennepin County
  - 820464, 1999-2002 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    County of Schenectady
  - 82486, 2003-2006 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - 820487, 1990-1993 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    Metropolitan Dade County
  - 820489, 2003-2006 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    Miami-Dade Fire Rescue Department
  - 820490, 2002-2004 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    County of Milwaukee
  - 820496, 2003-2006 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - 820498, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - 820527, 1999-2005 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    Contra Costa County
  - 820528, 1999-2005 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - 820535, 2002-2004 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    County of Rockland
  - 820541, 2000-2004 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - 820578, 1992-1996 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    County of Sonoma
  - 820586, 2002-2005 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    County of Santa Cruz
  - 820602, 1978-1987 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    County of Hudsons
  - 820608, 2000-2003 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    Niagara Frontier Transit Metro
  - 820609, 2002-2006 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    County of San Mateo
  - 820607, 1998-2000 (Box 40, Folder 36)
    County of Merced
  - 820610, 2002-2006 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - 820635, 2003-2005 (Box 40, Folder 38)
    County of Monterey
  - 820666, 1979-1989 (Box 40, Folder 39)
    County of Riverside
  - 820640, 2001-2004 (Box 40, Folder 40)
    City School District of New Rochelle
  - 820696, 2002-2004 (Box 40, Folder 41)
    San Joaquin County
  - 820698, 2002-2004 (Box 40, Folder 42)